21.com 2005-02-07

# 

#### Privacy Policy 

**Introduction**  
Your privacy is important, so CENTURY 21 Affiliated has created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the CENTURY 21 Affiliated web site (the "Site"), why we collect it, and how it is used. The terms "you," "your" and "yours" refer to all visitors of our Site. The terms "CENTURY 21 Affiliated," "we," "us" and "our" refer to CENTURY 21 Affiliated, its subsidiaries, affiliates and those we've contracted to make the Site available. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use . By accessing this Site and the content, information, products and services available on this Site (collectively the "Services"), you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy and other terms in our Terms of Use. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes, so we encourage you to visit this page often.

**Index**  
1\. Information We Collect; How We Collect It  
2\. Is Information Shared or Disclosed?  
3\. Some Examples of When We Share Your Information  
4\. How to Stop Sharing of Information  
5\. Security and Passwords  
6\. Emails Sent to You  
7\. Cookies  
8\. Children/Minors  
9\. Contacting CENTURY 21 Affiliated

**1\. Information We Collect; How We Collect It**  
We may request at times that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. Such personal information includes information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number, and other contact information, whether at work or at home. Generally some or all of this information is requested when you register on the Site.

CENTURY 21 Affiliated, its service providers and all vendors providing products or services through our Site use your personal information to, among other things: operate the Site and fulfill your requests; conduct research; and market or promote other products or services of interest to you.

CENTURY 21 Affiliated also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information and the pages you request. We intend to continue improving the content and function of our Site, and we monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help CENTURY 21 Affiliated provide content of interest to you, add and improve features of our Services and enhance the design and layout of our Site. We use cookies to recognize you when you return to the site in the future. This is done as a convenience to you so that you don't need to re-register."

**2\. Is Information Shared or Disclosed?**  
CENTURY 21 Affiliated may store and disclose personal information as allowed or required by applicable law, including making disclosures that are necessary or advisable to: 

(a) protect the rights, safety or property of users of our Site, the public, CENTURY 21 Affiliated or our suppliers; and 

(b) conform to legal or regulatory requirements. 

Under certain circumstances, CENTURY 21 Affiliated may choose to trade, sell or rent your personal information with trustworthy third parties. Also, if CENTURY 21 Affiliated should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell the information you provide to CENTURY 21 Affiliated on this Site to a third party or share your personal information with any company with whom we merge. Users who would rather not provide any of the information requested by our registration process do not need to register with CENTURY 21 Affiliated. You can still view some of the content available on our Site without registering. You will, however, need to register to access most of the information available on our Site.

**3\. Some Examples of When We Share Your Information**  
We work with many publishers and their agents to provide you with access to the content available on this Site. Accordingly, certain items and content on the Site are delivered to you by companies other than CENTURY 21 Affiliated. This includes property and community information. In the cases where you purchase an item on our Site that is fulfilled by another company, you become a customer of the publisher or seller of that item, and we will provide certain of your personal information to that third party. We typically provide personal information such as the item purchased, the price you paid, your name, your email address and your mailing address. We may also ask you to provide us with certain marketing or demographic information at the time of your purchase. If you choose to provide us with any such marketing or demographic information, we may be contractually obligated to share this information with the applicable third party. We generally have no control over how the third party will use your personal information, which might include direct marketing of other products from the same company, or the marketing of your name and address to other companies for the purpose of marketing other products and services to you.

In any case, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the use or misuse of your personal information by third parties from which you purchase items through the Services or by third parties with whom we have marketing and other partnerships.

**4\. How to Stop Sharing of Information**  
You can let us know that you do not wish to receive information about new features and special offers by sending an e-mail to [privacy@c21affiliated.com](mailto:privacy@c21affiliated.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). You can also "opt-out" of having your information shared by sending and email to [privacy@c21affiliated.com](mailto:privacy@c21affiliated.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). Please note that you will not be able to opt out of CENTURY 21 Affiliated sharing certain of your personal information with a third party from whom you choose to purchase items through this Site. To cancel your CENTURY 21 Affiliated account, you will need to contact info@c21affiliated.com.

**5\. Security and Passwords**  
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. CENTURY 21 Affiliated intends to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect such information from unauthorized access or disclosure. While we make efforts to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

When your password is requested on this Site, we use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to present secure pages to protect that information. You can tell if you are using a secure server by looking at the bottom of your browser window. In Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer, you will see a lock icon. When the symbol is unbroken or the padlock appears to be in its closed state, the page is encrypted and therefore secure. If you wish to take advantage of the latest encryption standards, be sure you have the latest version of the browser you use. You can download the latest version from the Netscape or Microsoft web sites. Using beta versions of browsers is not recommended.

You can change your password at any time, and you can set a new password in case you forgot your old one which is accessible from our home page. Please keep your password in a safe place and do not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is especially important if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

Your account is protected by your password. You choose a password when you first start an account with us. Your password needs to:   
\- be at least 5 characters long (case sensitive)  
\- include both numbers and letters  
\- not contain symbols (*, $, #, %, etc.)  
Make sure to select a password that is not obvious. A good password includes seemingly random letters and numbers, for example, F3M8N1.

**6\. Emails Sent to You**  
We will send you emails relating to certain activities including when you request property information. We may send you email notices about new features, products and services. We may also send you email notices regarding Site and service announcements containing important information about the Services. You can unsubscribe to these notifications by following the 'unsubscribe' instructions at the bottom of the email you receive. 

**7\. Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser receives from web sites and stores on your computer's hard drive. CENTURY 21 Affiliated uses cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit CENTURY 21 Affiliated to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. CENTURY 21 Affiliated (or a third-party provider we contract with) may occasionally include specific tags (also known as "clear gifs" or "web beacons") on selected web pages or email messages to customers. The tags provide statistical information to CENTURY 21 Affiliated so we can better understand what communications are successful. 

**8\. Children/Minors**  
This Site is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. CENTURY 21 Affiliated does not sell products for purchase by children. Any person who provides their information to CENTURY 21 Affiliated through the registration page for new users or any other part of the Site represents to CENTURY 21 Affiliated that they are 18 years of age or older.

**9\. Contacting CENTURY 21 Affiliated**  
Our goal is to respect your privacy. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact [privacy@c21affiliated.com](mailto:privacy@c21affiliated.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). CENTURY 21 Affiliated welcomes your comments and questions.
